

# Nikola Rosic

iOS developer

Novi Sad, Serbia 0603444707 · <u>rosicnikola90@gmail.com</u>

⇔ LinkedIn, GitHub

#### **Skills**

Swift

Objective C

**UIKit Framework** 

xCode

MVC design pattern

MVVM design pattern

3rd party SDKs and API(S)

integration

**RESTful APIs** 

Prioritization

Problem solving

Collaboration

Communication

Languages

English

Serbian

**Hobbies** 

Video games Astronomy

### **Profile**

Organized, collaborative, and highly passionate iOS developer with 6+ month of professional experience in dynamic work environment. Some of application on app store that i am working on:

\*eFinity

https://apps.apple.com/us/app/efinity/id1528523731

Some of features added by me: interactive SVG map, ticket reservation, ticket payment info, UI changes, bug fixing and much more

\* NisNocu

https://apps.apple.com/us/app/nisnocu/id1534623966

Some of features added by me: event representation, seat booking, SMS notifications, UI and UX changes

\*TimeTracking

https://apps.apple.com/us/app/simula-time-track/id1445561620

Some of features added by me: task attachment, clocks UI bugs and much more

## **Employment History**

sea operations (import/export), cargo-partner, Novi Sad

November 2017 — June 2021

iOS developer, Simula, Novi Sad

June 2021 - Present

#### **Education**

traffic engineering, Faculty of technical science, Novi Sad

April 2009 - April 2014